[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '引っ越します' read in word?",
        "answer": "Переїжджати"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '通います' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відвідувати"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '側' read in word?",
        "answer": "Сторона, бік"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '頃' read in word?",
        "answer": "Період, час, пора"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '言葉' read in word?",
        "answer": "слово"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '接頭辞' read in word?",
        "answer": "префікс"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '接尾辞' read in word?",
        "answer": "суфікс"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '大学校' read in word?",
        "answer": "велика школа"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新自転車' read in word?",
        "answer": "новий велосипед"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '不親切な' read in word?",
        "answer": "не дружній"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '御住所' read in word?",
        "answer": "адреса (ввічливо)"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji '研究所' read in word?",
        "answer": "лабораторія"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '映画館' read in word?",
        "answer": "кінотеатр"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the kanji '音楽家' read in word?",
        "answer": "музикант"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the kanji '動物園' read in word?",
        "answer": "зоопарк"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the kanji '動物' read in word?",
        "answer": "тварина"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the kanji '園' read in word?",
        "answer": "парк"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the kanji '図書館' read in word?",
        "answer": "бібліотека"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the kanji '古本屋' read in word?",
        "answer": "старий книжний"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新聞社' read in word?",
        "answer": "видання газет"
    },
    {
        "id": "21",
        "question": "How is the kanji '不有名' read in word?",
        "answer": "не популярний"
    },
    {
        "id": "22",
        "question": "How is the kanji '御飯' read in word?",
        "answer": "їжа, рис"
    },
    {
        "id": "23",
        "question": "How is the kanji '不人気' read in word?",
        "answer": "не популярний"
    },
    {
        "id": "24",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新公園' read in word?",
        "answer": "новий парк"
    },
    {
        "id": "25",
        "question": "How is the kanji '銀行家' read in word?",
        "answer": "банкір"
    },
    {
        "id": "26",
        "question": "How is the kanji '作家' read in word?",
        "answer": "письменник"
    },
    {
        "id": "27",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新作分' read in word?",
        "answer": "новий твір"
    },
    {
        "id": "28",
        "question": "How is the kanji '所' read in word?",
        "answer": "місце"
    },
    {
        "id": "29",
        "question": "How is the kanji '狭くて、小さいところ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Вузькі, малі місця"
    },
    {
        "id": "30",
        "question": "How is the kanji '住所' read in word?",
        "answer": "адреса"
    },
    {
        "id": "31",
        "question": "How is the kanji '近所' read in word?",
        "answer": "околиця"
    },
    {
        "id": "32",
        "question": "How is the kanji '名所' read in word?",
        "answer": "визначні місця"
    },
    {
        "id": "33",
        "question": "How is the kanji '特別な仕事すること' read in word?",
        "answer": "роблять особливу роботу"
    },
    {
        "id": "34",
        "question": "How is the kanji '研究所' read in word?",
        "answer": "лабораторія"
    },
    {
        "id": "35",
        "question": "How is the kanji '市役所' read in word?",
        "answer": "посольство"
    },
    {
        "id": "36",
        "question": "How is the kanji '刑務所' read in word?",
        "answer": "в’язниця"
    },
    {
        "id": "37",
        "question": "How is the kanji '場' read in word?",
        "answer": "місце"
    },
    {
        "id": "38",
        "question": "How is the kanji '人が集まる所です' read in word?",
        "answer": "місце, де збираються люди"
    },
    {
        "id": "39",
        "question": "How is the kanji '会場' read in word?",
        "answer": "зал засідань"
    },
    {
        "id": "40",
        "question": "How is the kanji '浴場' read in word?",
        "answer": "баня, душ"
    },
    {
        "id": "41",
        "question": "How is the kanji '市場' read in word?",
        "answer": "ринок, базар"
    },
    {
        "id": "42",
        "question": "How is the kanji '何か行うことです' read in word?",
        "answer": "щось трапляється(івенти, події)"
    },
    {
        "id": "43",
        "question": "How is the kanji '劇場' read in word?",
        "answer": "театр"
    },
    {
        "id": "44",
        "question": "How is the kanji '式場' read in word?",
        "answer": "зал церемонії"
    },
    {
        "id": "45",
        "question": "How is the kanji '戦場' read in word?",
        "answer": "фронт, поле бою"
    },
    {
        "id": "46",
        "question": "How is the kanji '区' read in word?",
        "answer": "сторожити"
    },
    {
        "id": "47",
        "question": "How is the kanji '土地を分けたところ' read in word?",
        "answer": "земельні ділянки поділені"
    },
    {
        "id": "48",
        "question": "How is the kanji '学区' read in word?",
        "answer": "шкільний район"
    },
    {
        "id": "49",
        "question": "How is the kanji '特区' read in word?",
        "answer": "спеціальна зона"
    },
    {
        "id": "50",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新宿区' read in word?",
        "answer": "район Шінджюку"
    },
    {
        "id": "51",
        "question": "How is the kanji '地' read in word?",
        "answer": "земля"
    },
    {
        "id": "52",
        "question": "How is the kanji '地面や土地' read in word?",
        "answer": "земельні ділянки і поверхня землі"
    },
    {
        "id": "53",
        "question": "How is the kanji '借地' read in word?",
        "answer": "оренда землі"
    },
    {
        "id": "54",
        "question": "How is the kanji '墓地' read in word?",
        "answer": "цвинтар"
    },
    {
        "id": "55",
        "question": "How is the kanji '山地' read in word?",
        "answer": "скеляста місцина"
    }
]